Nishant Priyadarshi

Private Address

Flat No. 26/803, Seawood Estates NRI Complex, Sector 56, Seawoods

Navi Mumbai, India Mobile: +91-7718876201

Email: meetnishant123@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://in.linkedin.com/in/nishant-priyadarshi-07143040

Date of Birth 01 March 1980

Languages

English, Hindi

Professional Summary

9 years experience in Insurance across multiple functions including Customer Service, Operations, Process Excellence and Project Management; Management of end-to-end business, technology & change management projects for the digital channel.

Knowledge & Skills

- Online Sales &E-Commerce
- Change Management
- Project Management

- Business Processes
- Strategic Alliances
- Leadership Experience

Work Experience

Jan 2013-Present

Bharti AXA General Insurance, India

One of India's fastest growing multi-line general insurers with GWP of USD 310 million. 3rd largest Digital General Insurer in the Country.

Manager - Digital Business Operations and Telesales

- Establish business processes, defining continuous improvement processes, implementing and training team. Developing/aligning the customer's behaviors and unpinning Customer Satisfaction culture.
- Handling product and process queries and improvements across insurance products.
- Coordinates with different departments, finance, IT, U/w, Ops for fast resolution and corrective measures.
- Part of e-portal optimization and website revamp projects.
- Lead major IT deployments of strategic priorities.
- Project on Cross-selling of GI products from Bharti AXA Life Insurance.
- Project on minimizing the customer complaint through process improvement.
- Plan & establish SOP, internal controls, procedures, MIS, TAT for Policy Issuance for Customer Service, Telesales and Aggregators.
- Conducting process audits as well as suggesting and implementing process improvement related changes within the various functions in the department.
- Handling Business and IT projects aimed at improving the company's Digital presence

May 2007 - Dec 2012

Reliance General Ins. Co. Ltd.

India's 7th largest private General insurance company with GWP of USD 103 million

Regional Service Manager – Branch Operations

- Custodian of Policy, endorsements, refunds, complaints for all GI products.
- To define processes for all the undertaken activities. A daily Dashboard to the stakeholders.
- Training team on various processes of bank reconciliation, products and system for smooth business processing.
- Worked on Project -Bad Debt Recovery It was implemented across the branches in India.

Education

•	Post Graduate Programme in Management	2005 - 2007
	Xavier Institute of Social Service, Ranchi, India	
•	B. Sc (Honors)	1999 - 2004
	B. S. College, Magadh University, India	

Recent Awards and Accolades

 AXA Value Awards – Presented for exhibiting Innovation and Teamwork 	2014
 Reliance Value Awards – Shining STAR – In managing operational activities 	2009 - 2011